The Princess Sapphire
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Princess Knight,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Forty-Third Episode
The Spider Island
Hey!
But this is a ship in the shape
of a swan! How big and beautiful it is!
I'll run to the castle right away
to tell Sapphire!
Sapphire, wake up! In the lake
there's a beautiful swan-ship!
- Look! Isn't it magnificent?
- A swan-ship?!
It's a strange shape for a ship.
I wonder who it belongs to..!
Come on, let's go see it up close.
I'd like to try to get on board.
Please, come aboard if you like!
Grand Duke Duralumin
had this ship built..
...specially for you, Prince.
You may come aboard!
You know, the Grand Duke is very keen
on you having a good time!
It's a bit strange
that the Grand Duke desires this,
but the ship is inviting.
I hope you will come aboard,
Prince.
Very well, we will go on board
and have a look.
My dear little son!
You know, Plastic, I have a wonderful
gift for you.
A sweet?
I would never give you
such an insignificant gift.
The whole of Silverland will be yours,
tomorrow!
Have you seen
that beautiful swan-ship?
As soon as Sapphire
sets foot on it,
it will sail towards the lonely
island of roses!
Who is it?
- Ah, it's you!
- Everything is going for the best
- Magnificent!
- Everything is ready.
We have scrupulously followed
your instructions.
The ship was built
as you commanded.
Also the work on the island
has been completed...
...according to your orders.
The Princess will disappear
on the deserted island...
...and no one will notice.
Then everything will go according to plan.
Good!
That ship is really beautiful!
How nice! It would be fun
to take a trip on this ship!
We could sail for a long time.
Look, Tink! The ship has set sail!
It's sailing by itself!
Help! Help!
- Save us! Help!
- Hey! Hey!
Who's shouting?
Help! Help!
But it's Sapphire!
Franz! Franz!
Please, help us!
- Prince Franz!
- Help, Franz!
Unfortunately, he can't do anything
Sapphire, the rudder isn't working!
We almost crashed!
Franz followed us
onto the cliff!
Sapphire, I'll try to save you!
How brave he is!
I'm happy
to be able to be near you.
It's raining...
What a downpour!
Why don't you come under here
to take shelter?
It's all the same,
we're fine here too.
What a magnificent island this is!
It's full of roses!
But there's something strange...
These roses are truly beautiful,
- but they don't smell at all.
- This island is strange, too.
Let's try to find out why.
Look, a tunnel of roses!
Hey! Wait! Wait, hat!
Where did Tink go?
He was right behind us!
Tink! Tink!
- Tink!
- Tink, where are you?
Tink, answer me! Tink!
Look, Franz: the roses!
Sapphire, watch out!
There's something strange.
- Look, Franz!
- And what do these cats want?
Sapphire, take cover behind me!
If they want to harm us,
I will face them with my sword.
I don't believe they are just cats.
Perhaps they are evil spirits.
I will fight too!
There's no need, leave it to me.
Watch out, they're circling us!
- Franz!
- Sapphire!
Franz!
The cats are tearing my dress!
Sapphire!
What is this?
The mysterious knight
is not afraid of you, you nasty cats!
But where could Franz have ended up
now?
Franz, where are you?
Franz, answer me!
Franz! Tink! Where are you?
Answer, quick!
- Franz! Tink!
- Sapphire!
But you are the mysterious knight!
- Don't worry, I'll free you now.
- Thank you.
Perhaps Prince Franz
has also been captured by the cats.
You can't say that this
is a normal island.
I let myself get caught
like a fool!
I'll take care of looking for Franz
But how will you look for him
on such a dangerous island?
I'll find him, you'll see!
How strange...! This spiderweb
is as thick as a rope.
I must find out who made it
Have you lost consciousness, Franz?
Who are you?
Why have you captured me?
You want to know who I am? I am
the Spider-Man, master of the island.
I was waiting for you, because I knew
the swan ship had set sail.
My master ordered me
to kill Princess Sapphire!
But I didn't expect her
lover to be with her!
So, at this point,
I’ll get rid of you first!
So it was all a
prearranged plan, wasn't it?
Exactly! That's why you'll share
the fate of your dear Princess!
You should be happy, shouldn't you?
Franz!
The mysterious knight!
I've come to save you.
Dammit,
this rope won't break!
It's no ordinary rope.
I have an idea, Tink! Look
for some water somewhere!
- Right away!
- What happened to Princess Sapphire?
Sapphire is doing just
fine, don't worry about her.
Thank goodness! But
you, mysterious knight,
Why do you always
appear when she isn't here?
There's no time
now to discuss this.
We have to escape from here
while the spider-man is sleeping.
I found the water, but
what do you need it for?
Pour it on him!
See? Now let's run! Quick!
The boy has escaped!
I'll catch him again!
I can't go on anymore!
Come on, Tink, or he'll catch us!
You go on ahead, I'm too tired!
A scratch will be enough
with these poisoned stilettos...
...to make you lose your life!
And now for the two of you!
Franz is wounded and the
poison is starting to take effect.
- What do you plan to do?
- We must leave here immediately.
And we must look for the antidote!
I'll make you pay for my wound!
Tink, I've heard that
where an evil monster lives...
...a plant grows that
neutralizes the poison.
Try looking around here. Maybe
you'll be able to find this plant.
Yes, I'll find it for sure!
- Oh, Sapphire...
- Yes, I'm here.
- Sapphire... Sapphire!
- The fever is making him delirious.
Poor Franz! If we don't
find the antidote, he will die
Don't worry, Franz!
The mysterious knight
will try once more.
Courage, Franz!
Sapphire!
I am beside you. Don't worry,
Franz, you'll be saved!
Thank you, Sapphire.
Here is the herb! I found it!
It will remove the effect of the
Spider-Man's poison!
But how?
Have you returned again, Sapphire?
Shut up!
- Give me the plant immediately.
- Here it is!
Let's hope
it really works..
Now he should recover.
There are no excuses
that will hold up!
Of course I didn't foresee that
Franz would come here too,
but you're a professional! You cannot
be defeated by a boy!
He hasn't beaten me yet!
Besides, I wounded him
with the poisoned stiletto..
...when he pierced me. By now
the poison will have already taken effect.
I am here to receive from you
Sapphire's body!
This is the promise
that you made me.
Are you so inept as to retreat
over a small wound?
Go and kill Sapphire with
the web you are so proud of!
I will return to the island as soon
as I know she has been finished off!
Go now!
Where did Sapphire go?
What? Sapphire was here?!
Yes! She was beside me and
tended to me all night long.
Tink has already sent her
home flying on the back of a swan.
But then it wasn't her last night!
You must have dreamed of
her in your feverish delirium.
Now the two of us must
think about repairing the ship.
Rest a bit more.
Now the rudder works!
I fixed the hull.
We can set off again.
No, you can't!
Princess Sapphire, I will kill you!
- Spider-Man!
- You are dressed in strange clothes
but it's you, Sapphire, isn't it?
No, I am
the mysterious knight!
It doesn't matter! Whoever you are,
I won't leave you alive!
You, my friends,
take care of the brat.
Help!
I'll show you!
I'm not afraid of you..!
I have a very powerful drug,
that you will like and that will make you sleep!
Take that!
It's the end for me!
- Tink, are you okay?
- Yes!
The cats ate a drug
and now they are sleeping soundly.
Curse it, I didn't make it!
But it doesn't end here!
I won't give up so easily,
you little pests!
I will manage to kill you, Sapphire
and seize the throne,
sooner or later!
Sapphire, I will never forget...
...how sweet you were
taking care of me,
even if they say
that it was a dream
Franz, I'm glad
that you said it.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP